videodeals.com 2012-06-08

# VideoDeals

VideoDeals.com is owned by VideoDeals.com S.A., Luxembourg and licensed to Videodeals.com Benelux B.V. (hereinafter VideoDeals). A responsible handling of personal data of users is of great importance to VideoDeals. Personal data of our customers is carefully being processed and protected. In doing so VideoDeals complies with the requirements set out in the Data Protection Act and the Telecommunications Act. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform the customer about, how VideoDeals uses the personally data about its customers which is collected on or through our website, and how the customer can change or delete the data. This Privacy Statement applies only to this website and not to other websites for which links are provided on this site. Those are the responsibility of third parties.

By using the VideoDeals Service, buying a VideoDeal, and / or accepting the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Statement by actively checking the therefore provided box (opt-in), the buyer expressly agrees that VideoDeals uses and processes his / her personal data in a manner and for the purposes specified and stated in this document. If the customer's (additional) consent is required for the aforementioned use and processing, because his / her email has to be used by the partner in order to execute the purchase of the deal, VideoDeals will separately request this information from the customer.

The customer can choose to revoke his / her consent at any time without giving any reason, by sending an email to [legal@videodeals.com](mailto:legal@videodeals.com).

If the customer is under 18 and wants to use one or more of the VideoDeals Services, by which VideoDeals asks permission for the processing of personal data, parental consent is required. In that case, the customer guarantees that his / her parents gave or have given their permission.

VideoDeals processes personal data in four situations:

  1. for customers who wish to use VideoDeals Services and want to receive daily exclusive deals from, or news about VideoDeals per e-mail or other means of communications including messages by mobile phone, tablet or television;
  2. for customers who wants to offer or sell a VideoDeal, or: who want to make use of one or more deals and want to create an account for that purpose;
  3. for customers who intend to make their own Commercial Videos available via the Videodeals.com Site, or for customers who intend to attach a deal to their video and want to create an account for that purpose;
  4. 4) for Professional Merchants who wants to offer their goods / services for sale on the VideoDeals.com Site using a Commercial Video and want to create an Merchant Account for that purpose.

The personal data which is processed in situation 1), situation 2 and 3) and situation 4) is being handled differently:

With regard to the first situation VideoDeals only processes the email address and / or mobile telephone number of the customer. This e-mail address or mobile number is then used for the daily e-mailing of exclusive deals by VideoDeals which we offer for or on behalf of our affiliated Merchants, or for e-mailing our own news.

With regard to the second and third situation, VideoDeals needs more information from the customer regarding to, creating an account, publishing a Commercial Video online, and executing the VideoDeal. In this case VideoDeals processes, besides the email address - only if necessary - other, hereafter mentioned personal data, solely for the purpose of creating an account, publishing the Commercial Video, and achieving the customer’s purchase of the VideoDeal. For the purchasing process VideoDeals also refers to Article 6 of our Terms and Conditions, which can be consulted or summoned at any time at www.videodeals.com/Home/Terms.

Concerning the fourth situation, VideoDeals needs more details of the Professional Merchant who wants to create an account and offer its goods / services for sale on the VideoDeals.com Site. In this case, the hereafter mentioned data of the company of the affiliated Professional Merchant will be processed, solely for the purpose of creating a Merchant Account and executing the payment to the Professional Merchant.

The basic principle is that no personal details are provided or disclosed by VideoDeals to third parties. Personal details of customers only will be provided to third party affiliated Professional Merchants when such information is necessary for the execution of the VideoDeal. The Professional Merchant is also bound by this Privacy Statement.

Video Deals collects and processes the following personal data of the customer:

  * Name and address (name and address details)
  * Mobile phone
  * E-mail
  * IP address
  * Bank account / credit card details

And if the customer voluntarily has given the hereafter mentioned personal data:

  * Date of birth
  * Gender
  * Phone

In the case of a professional Merchant who wishes to offers goods / services for sale on the VideoDeals.com Site and therefore wants to register by creating a Merchant Account:

  * Name, address, establishment and Company Registration number
  * Mobile and fixed telephone number
  * Bank account information including name, account number, IBAN and BIC number
  * Additional data necessary to transfer the payment of a VideoDeal to the affiliated Professional Merchant.

VideoDeals uses specific data such as IP-address, date of birth and gender in anonymised form for compiling anonymous statistics and reports, such as an annual report on the purchasing behaviour of women between the age of 20-25 in the province of North-Holland, who have logged into VideoDeals.com. Although the customer isn’t recognizable or traceable in any way on the basis of this anonymous data, and therefore no processing of personal data takes place, VideoDeals finds it conscientious to mention this 'anonymous' purpose.

VideoDeals strives to be fully transparent in the processing of personal data of its customers and will always indicate which data is being processed and for what purpose. The customer may ask at any time if VideoDeals processes his / her personal data and also may request access to that data, the purpose the data is being processed for, and have it corrected, added or deleted. For this purpose the customer can send an e-mail, stating his / her name and address, to the VideoDeals helpdesk at: [legal@videodeals.com](mailto:legal@videodeals.com). Within 4 weeks the customer will receive a response.

The customer may always opt out and unsubscribe to the VideoDeals Services by clicking the link listed at the bottom of each newsletter and / or offer, or by e-mailing to: [servicecenter@videodeals.com](mailto:servicecenter@videodeals.com). VideoDeals removes the data of the customer and the customer will not receive e-mails or other messages anymore from VideoDeals.

By transferring or receiving your personal data via the VideoDeals.com Site we make use of safety procedures, including preventing unauthorized access to personal data. VideoDeals also makes use of (SSL) encryption technologies recognized as common standards within the IT sector. If we receive or transfer sensitive data such as financial information, we use a secure server. We also use a secure (SSL) server when you buy a VideoDeal. You will be informed of this by means of a screen that is shown on our website (popup). VideoDeals has taken technical and organizational measures to protect (the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we transfer or receive via our website) your personal information against loss or unauthorized processing. Please read our Privacy Statement for more information.

Common, anonymous visitor data, including the most requested pages, is also being tracked and processed on the VideoDeals website (s). The purpose of this is, among other reasons, to be able to optimize the design of the website so VideoDeals can further optimize its services. If VideoDeals captures such data, VideoDeals makes sure that this kind of data is in no way reducible to customers.

VideoDeals uses ‘cookies’ by providing her electronic services. A cookie is a small file sent by an Internet server and stored on the hard disk of your computer. This file keeps track of the website you have visited and contains some information about this visit. These cookies are used solely for making the usage of the website easier. The customer has the option to decline the cookies by adjusting the the web browser settings.

Videodeals.com uses cookies:

  * To record information which applies to you, including the web pages you have visited in order to go to our Site.
  * To record your previous activities on the Site, for the purpose of offering you a better service next time.
  * To ensure that you do not repeatedly receive the same ads / advertisements.
  * The adjust the content and presentation of the site, which information is based on your browser type or other information sent by the browser.

VideoDeals reserves the right to make unilateral changes to this Privacy statement. Changes or additions to this Privacy statement will be published here. We advise you to check the Privacy statement regularly. If such a change entails an extension or change of the purposes by which VideoDeals processes personal data, the customer shall be informed and, if necessary, VideoDeals will ask for the additional consent of the customer. For questions regarding our privacy statement, please contact:

  * By email: legal@videodeals.com
  * By telephone: +31 (0) 20 654 1981
  * By fax: +31 (0) 20 203 1099
  * By letter: Videodeals.com Benelux B.V., Attn. Legal Department

Parc Centre, Boeing Avenue 8, 1119 PB Schiphol Rijk, The Netherlands

This Privacy statement was made on the 26th of April 2012.
